<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Daniele Pannone</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Daniele Pannone</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hi-there&#34;&gt;Hi there&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Daniele Pannone, and I got my M.Sc. (2015) and Ph.D. (2018) in Computer Science from Sapienza University of Rome. From 2015 to 2024, I was part of the Computer Vision Laboratory (VisionLab) at the Department of Computer Science. Since 2020, I&amp;rsquo;ve been an Assistant Professor at the same Department. In 2024, I co-founded both the Prometheus Lab and 4AI, a startup at Sapienza focused on pushing the boundaries of artificial intelligence. That same year, I also became an NVidia Deep Learning University Ambassador. My research covers a lot of topics, including machine and deep learning, event recognition, object detection, person re-identification, signal analysis and processing, bioinformatics, human-computer interaction, and robotics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research Topics</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My research interests concern the design of Computer Vision, Machine and Deep Learning algorithms for the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dronistics, e.g., automatic mosaic of areas of interest (mosaicking), identification of changes (change detection), identification and classification of elements present in the scene (object detection and classification);&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;EEG Signal Analysis;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wi-Fi Sensing;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analysis of medical images;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Augmented and Virtual Reality;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Re-Identification of subjects;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automatic lie detection;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Rehabilitation with serious games;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Machine and Deep Learning in DNA Sequencing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
